<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- ⚠️ 自动生成 —— 请勿手改。改 packages/changelog/android.json 后运行 `pnpm changelog:gen`。 -->
<resources>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_7_0_0_title">Search everything from one place</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_7_0_0_detail">The magnifier on the overview searches domains, Workers, R2 buckets, D1 databases, KV namespaces and tunnels at once — tap a result to go straight there. And any resource can now be starred to the overview.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_7_0_1_title">Alert center</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_7_0_1_detail">The overview now gathers what needs attention — inactive domains, tunnels in a bad state and more — into a single card. Tap an item to jump right to it.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_7_0_2_title">Better live logs</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_7_0_2_detail">Live Worker logs now support keyword search and level filtering; long-press to copy a whole line, tap to expand the full detail and select any part of it. Pause now only freezes the view — logs keep arriving, so nothing is missing when you resume.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_7_0_3_title">SQL history and favorites</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_7_0_3_detail">D1 keeps your last 12 queries and lets you favorite the ones you reuse (saved per database). Results export to CSV in a tap, and table details now list indexes.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_7_0_4_title">Generate images with Workers AI</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_7_0_4_detail">The model playground now covers text-to-image models — type a prompt, get a picture, then share or save it.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_7_0_5_title">Preview R2 objects</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_7_0_5_detail">Tap an R2 object to preview it: images show inline, JSON is formatted automatically, and text can be searched with a match count. Oversized objects still suggest downloading instead.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_6_0_title">Quickly bind R2 buckets</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_6_0_detail">Resource bindings now cover R2 — attach an existing bucket to a Worker, and unbind it just like D1 / KV.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_6_1_title">Smoother editing for long scripts</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_6_1_detail">Rebuilt the Worker code editor’s input handling so typing stays smooth in long scripts.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_5_0_title">One-tap workers.dev URL</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_5_0_detail">When a Worker’s workers.dev subdomain is on, its full URL now shows right there — tap to open.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_5_1_title">Quickly bind D1 / KV</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_5_1_detail">Bind an existing D1 database or KV namespace to a Worker right from the bindings page — and unbind just as easily.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_5_2_title">Fixed crash when editing long scripts</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_5_2_detail">Fixed a crash that could occur when editing a longer Worker script.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_4_0_title">Account usage overview</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_4_0_detail">The overview now has a usage module — see Workers, R2, D1 and KV usage against their quotas at a glance, with plan switching and per-metric details.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_4_1_title">Worker deployment history and delete</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_4_1_detail">View a Worker’s past deployments and delete old ones, plus edit and delete Workers.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_4_2_title">More storage management</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_4_2_detail">Create and delete KV namespaces and R2 buckets, drop D1 tables, and delete Pages deployments.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_0_0_title">Pages custom domains</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_0_0_detail">Manage custom domains right inside a Pages project: add, remove, re-validate, and check DNS status — with one-tap CNAME setup when the domain’s zone is on your account.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_0_1_title">List sorting</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_6_0_1_detail">Workers and Pages lists can now be sorted by name (default), date created, or recently updated — your choice is remembered.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_5_0_0_title">No-login developer toolbox</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_5_0_0_detail">A set of handy network tools you can use without signing in: DNS lookup, SSL certificate inspection, HTTP headers, WHOIS, IP geolocation, a CIDR calculator and Cloudflare trace — reachable right from the login screen.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_5_0_1_title">Push Center</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_5_0_1_detail">A built-in push service: get your own endpoint and send messages to this device with a simple curl or script — with titles, groups and an inbox. No Cloudflare sign-in required.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_5_0_2_title">Cloudflare alerts on your phone</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_5_0_2_detail">Once signed in, manage your Cloudflare alert policies right here: pick the alert types you care about (DDoS, health checks, certificate expiry, Workers error rate and more) and wire them to the Push Center in one tap, so events land on this device. Requires a domain on a Pro or higher plan.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_4_2_0_title">Workers AI improvements</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_4_2_0_detail">Browse models grouped by task type, view model details, and the text-generation test run is fixed.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_4_0_title">New Developer Platform</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_4_0_detail">Workers now sits alongside Workers AI, AI Gateway, Queues, Hyperdrive, Durable Objects and Pages in a single Developer Platform hub.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_4_1_title">Cache Rules, Rate Limiting &amp; Email Routing</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_4_1_detail">Zones gain Cache Rules and Rate Limiting rules, plus Email Routing with forwarding rules and destination addresses.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_4_2_title">Load Balancing, Zero Trust &amp; Bulk Redirects</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_4_2_detail">New load balancers (with pool health), Zero Trust (Access apps and Gateway rule toggles), and Bulk Redirect lists and items.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_4_3_title">AI assistant &amp; visual WAF</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_4_3_detail">A new AI assistant powered by Workers AI; WAF rules can be built visually or generated from natural language.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_4_4_title">R2 in Files, traffic map &amp; audit log</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_4_4_detail">Browse, upload, rename, move and delete R2 objects in the system Files app; analytics adds traffic by country; Settings adds an account audit log; Pages shows deployments with one-tap retry or rollback.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_3_0_title">Domain security suite</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_3_0_detail">New SSL/TLS encryption modes and edge certificates, Universal SSL toggle, Transform Rules, IP access rules, plus HTTP/2·HTTP/3·Brotli and other performance and cache controls.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_3_1_title">R2 upgrade &amp; purge by URL</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_3_1_detail">R2 now supports folder browsing, object copy/move, and per-bucket CORS and public access settings; cache purge adds “purge by URL”.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_3_2_title">Home widget, live logs &amp; wider support</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_3_2_detail">A new daybreak “account overview” home widget; live tail logs are promoted to Live Updates (Android 16); Help &amp; Feedback can attach a diagnostic log; now supports Android 9 and above.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_1_0_title">From viewing to managing</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_1_0_detail">You can now add domains, create and delete D1 databases and tunnels, manage Worker variables/secrets/triggers/domains, and a tunnel’s public hostname routes.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_0_0_title">One-tap OAuth sign-in</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_0_0_detail">Sign in with Cloudflare\'s official authorization — no API tokens to paste.</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_0_1_title">Domains · Workers · Storage</string>
    <string name="whatsnew_1_0_1_detail">DNS, analytics, WAF, Snippets, Workers live logs, and R2/D1/KV storage — all in one place.</string>
</resources>
